<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HitechGroup</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_full_screen_image">FullScreenImage</string>

    <string name="text_aboutus_homefragment">HITECH GROUP began its operations from the City of
        Nawabs- Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh, India. Since then we are carrying out various
        residential and commercial projects to cater the needs and requirements of people at
        affordable rates along with excellent quality. The upcoming government projects are going
        to give a new dimension to the City of Nawabs-Lucknow. Lucknow will be a new blended hub of
        both culture and technology. This will result in mushrooming various job opportunities at each
        and every corner of this city thereby welcoming individuals from different regions to fulfill their
        dreams. Our company is determined to greet each of them with comfortable and affordable environment
        and providing healthy residential and profitable commercial spaces without compromising with the quality.</string>

    <string name="text_aboutus_homefragment2">On the other hand, we denounce with righteous indignation and dislike men who are so beguiled .</string>


    <string name="title_activity_full_screen_image_viewpager">FullScreenImageViewpager</string>
    <string name="title_activity_full_screen_image_view_pager">FullScreenImageViewPager</string>
    <string name="title_activity_full_screen_view_pager">FullScreenViewPager</string>
    <string name="aboutus_text">HITECH GROUP began its operations from the City of Nawabs- Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh,
        India. Since then we are carrying out various residential and commercial projects to cater the needs and
        requirements of people at affordable rates along with excellent quality. The upcoming government projects
        are going to give a new dimension to the City of Nawabs-Lucknow. Lucknow will be a new blended hub of both
        culture and technology. This will result in mushrooming various job opportunities at each and every corner
        of this city thereby welcoming individuals from different regions to fulfill their dreams. Our company is
        determined to greet each of them with comfortable and affordable environment
        and providing healthy residential and profitable commercial
        spaces without compromising with the quality.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_contact_us">ContactUs</string>
    <string name="title_activity_hitech_farm">HitechFarm</string>

    <string name="Chairmansoverview">Our Basic philosphy is make to significant contribution to the development our contry.
        we aim to cater the need of each segment of the society.HITECH GROUP is strongly commited towards providing the strong
    infrastructure.Our Business is based on strong realties and this provide us ease to keep transperency with our clients
    Providing ehic living, working and shopping enviourment to the people give us delight and satisfaction.Our Group is strongly
    dedicated towards its corporate social responsibility.Lastly I want to thank all my associates and team members who are working
    with us fully determination, devotion and commitment.</string>

    <string name="title_activity_vision_mission">VisionMissionActivity</string>
    <string name="our_vision">Our Vision is not bounded just to the state but to be an international leading Real
        estate agent, and be the company of first choice amongst our clients to address their needs across all
        realty verticals. To fulfill growing aspirations of our customers by building world class and environment
        friendly real estate solutions and redefining the standards of life style by engaging ourselves in
        the business of Real Estate Development including development of land, constructing and marketing
        of the same, with an intention of serving the society and community in general

        with the total dedication, commitment, with a focused purpose while maintaining the highest standards of excellence.</string>
<string name="our_mission">Our Mission is to establish long term healthy relationships with our clients, while
    offering an exceptionallevel of service and commitment to all their commercial, residential and industrial real estate needs.</string>

    <string name="historyoverview">HITECH GROUP began its operations from the City of Nawabs- Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh,
        India. Since then we are carrying out various residential and commercial projects to cater the needs and
        requirements of people at affordable rates along with excellent quality.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fragment">FragmentActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_gallery">GalleryActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_project">ProjectActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Login</string>




    <string name="text_aboutus_homefragment_linear">
<![CDATA[
<html>
 <head></head>
 <body style="text-align:justify;color:gray;background-color:white;">

        HITECH GROUP began its operations from the City of
        Nawabs- Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh, India. Since then we are carrying out various
        residential and commercial projects to cater the needs and requirements of people at
        affordable rates along with excellent quality. The upcoming government projects are going
        to give a new dimension to the City of Nawabs-Lucknow. Lucknow will be a new blended hub of
        both culture and technology. This will result in mushrooming various job opportunities at each
        and every corner of this city thereby welcoming individuals from different regions to fulfill their
        dreams. Our company is determined to greet each of them with comfortable and affordable environment
        and providing healthy residential and profitable commercial spaces without compromising with the quality.</string>


 </body>
</html>
]]>
</string>


    <string name="text_aboutus_homefragment2_linear">
<![CDATA[
<html>
 <head></head>
 <body style="text-align:justify;color:white;background-color:#6d883e;">
<font size="2">
       On the other hand, we denounce with righteous indignation and dislike men who are so beguiled.

</font>
 </body>
</html>
]]>



</string>

    <string name="navigation_item_1">Home</string>
    <string name="navigation_item_2">Events</string>
    <string name="starred_string">Starred</string>

    <string name="dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="team">Team</string>
    <string name="business">Business</string>
    <string name="income">Income</string>
    <string name="epins">ePins</string>
    <string name="rewards">Rewards</string>

    <string name="closeDrawer">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="openDrawer">Navigation View Closed</string>

<string name="image1">Image1</string>
    <string name="image2">Image2</string>
    <string name="image3">Image3</string>
    <string name="image4">Image4</string>




</resources>
